export default [
{
            id: 1,
            question: 'What is 3 - 1 ?',
            answers: ['2','0','3','1'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 2,
            question: 'What is 3 - 2 ?',
            answers: ['0','2','3','1'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 3,
            question: 'What is 3 - 3 ?',
            answers: ['0','1','3','2'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 4,
            question: 'What is 4 - 1 ?',
            answers: ['1','2','3','0'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 5,
            question: 'What is 4 - 2 ?',
            answers: ['0','3','1','2'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 6,
            question: 'What is 4 - 3 ?',
            answers: ['-2','0','1','-1'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 7,
            question: 'What is 5 - 1 ?',
            answers: ['4','1','3','2'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 8,
            question: 'What is 5 - 2 ?',
            answers: ['0','3','2','1'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 9,
            question: 'What is 5 - 3 ?',
            answers: ['2','0','-1','1'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 10,
            question: 'What is 6 - 1 ?',
            answers: ['5','3','4','2'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 11,
            question: 'What is 6 - 2 ?',
            answers: ['4','2','1','3'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 12,
            question: 'What is 6 - 3 ?',
            answers: ['2','1','0','3'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 13,
            question: 'What is 7 - 1 ?',
            answers: ['6','5','3','4'],
            correct: 1
    
        },
{
            id: 14,
            question: 'What is 7 - 2 ?',
            answers: ['4','5','3','2'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 15,
            question: 'What is 7 - 3 ?',
            answers: ['2','4','1','3'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 16,
            question: 'What is 8 - 1 ?',
            answers: ['6','5','4','7'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 17,
            question: 'What is 8 - 2 ?',
            answers: ['4','6','3','5'],
            correct: 2
    
        },
{
            id: 18,
            question: 'What is 8 - 3 ?',
            answers: ['4','2','3','5'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 19,
            question: 'What is 9 - 1 ?',
            answers: ['7','5','6','8'],
            correct: 4
    
        },
{
            id: 20,
            question: 'What is 9 - 2 ?',
            answers: ['5','4','7','6'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
{
            id: 21,
            question: 'What is 9 - 3 ?',
            answers: ['4','3','6','5'],
            correct: 3
    
        },
]
